Guide to the Mount Vernon Seminary and College Mount Vernon Seminary and College graphics, publications, and administrative material collection, 1890-2000 MVC0035.MS
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Photographs, 1875-2002; 1880-1999; Series 2
  - Students, 1875-1999; 1880-1950; Series 2 Subseries 6
    - Astrich, Mildred (Mrs. Paul P. Porter) - Class of 1912, Circa 1912; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Link, Ura Aetrone (Mrs. W. Rudolf Eckhardt) [Class of 1912], Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Lilly, Ella Marie [Class of 1913], 1912-1913; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Cole, Elcey Hoatson [Class of 1914], 1912-1914; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Anderson, Dorothy Palmes (Mrs. John Townsend, Jr.) - Class of 1915, 1912-1935; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Clephane, Beatrice Adaline, 1912-1938; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Lipps, Margaret Elizabeth [Class of 1914], Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - Davidson, Sara Morton (Mrs. Herbert A. May) [Class of 1916], 1914-1916; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - Henley, Martha [Class of 1916], 1914-1935; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - Fay, Helen [Class of 1915], Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 24)
    - Gates, Pauline, 1915; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 25)
    - Joy, Mildred (Mrs. Hugh Jewett Robertson) [Class of 1915], Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 26)
    - Crocker, Beulah, 1915-1917; Series 2 Suberies 6 (Box 36, Folder 27)
    - Acheson, Margaret - Class of 1916 (alum information), Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Gano, Vera, 1917; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 28)
    - Earle, Louise (Mrs. Arthur Vreeland Youngman) [Class of 1918], Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 29)
    - Hodson, Leila Payne (Mrs. James N. Hynson), 1918; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 30)
    - Lindahl, Vera (Mrs. R. M. Knox) [Class of 1918], Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 31)
    - Grosvenor, Mabel Harlakenden, 1919-1927; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 32)
    - Brisbin, Zerlina (Mrs. Joseph W. Lewis) - Class of 1920, Circa 1920; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Gregg, Mary Newton (Mrs. W. W. Young), 1920; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 33)
    - Undetermined class photo ca. early 20th century, Circa 1920; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Students at campus library, Circa 1920s; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 34)
    - Davison, Virginia Annette (Mrs. David Mackenzie Martin) [Class of 1924], 1920-1936; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 35)
    - Students in the Field House (Nebraska Avenue campus), Circa 1920-1940; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 36)
    - Family Christmas dinner, 1921; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Kilbourne, Dorothy (Mrs. William B. Gregg) [Class of 1921], Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 37)
    - Johnson, Winifred, 1921-1922; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 38)
    - Hayward, Mary Elizabeth (Mrs. Henry Bernard Arthur de Bruyne), 1921-1927; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 39)
    - Atwood, Gwendolyn Sophie (Mrs. Frank B. Kase) - Class of 1925, 1921-1940; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Group photograph, 1922; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Schonblom, Christine, 1922; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Connell, Jane Stickney (Mrs. John Ford Card) [Class of 1925] - biographical information, 1922-1936; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 40)
    - Davison, Harriet Elizabeth [Class of 1926] - biographical information, 1922-1936; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 41)
    - Hutton, Eleanor Post, 1923-1928; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 42)
    - Heckert, Margaret Louise (Mrs. George Edwards Dickson) [Class of 1925] - biographical information, 1923-1932; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 43)
    - Karel, Gladys J. (Mrs. Edward O. Gerhardy), 1923-1933; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 44)
    - Buck, Elizabeth (Mrs. Albert R. Hansen), 1923-1935; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 45)
    - Cunningham, Mary Elizabeth (Mrs. Clark Weymouth) [Class of 1927], 1923-1935; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 46)
    - Buehler, Barbara Kemp (biographical information), 1923-1936; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 47)
    - Herrick, Marguerite Florence [Class of 1928], 1924-1928; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 48)
    - Bentley, Marion Louise (Mrs. Albert H. Smith) - biographical information, 1924-1936; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Crabbs, Ruth Hamilton, 1925; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 49)
    - Curtis, Helen (Mrs. Edwin Charles Gamble) [Class of 1925], Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 50)
    - Boyd, Mary Grosvenor, 1925-1926; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Gannon, Kathleen Barrington (Mrs. John Frederick Bitzer) - biographical information, 1925-1926; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 51)
    - Bournique, Eugenie, 1925-1927; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - French, Eleanor Hurd, 1925-1927; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 52)
    - Evatt, Marjorie Franks, 1925-1929; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 53)
    - Erhard, Odessa Patchin [Class of 1927] - biographical information, 1925-1932; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 54)
    - Bettison, Marion "Betty" (Mrs. Kurt Schelling) - biographical information, 1925-1935; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - Bavinger, Kathryn "Connie" - Class of 1930, 1925-1936; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - Genius, Jeanette Morse, 1925-1936; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 55)
    - Hanna, Mary Eleanor (Mrs. Robert Strong Adams), 1925-1937; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 56)
    - Harris, Virginia (Mrs. George Boyd Webster) [Class of 1928] - biographical information, 1925-1937; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 57)
    - Gaut, Pauline Chambers (Mrs. Morton Boyd), 1926; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 58)
    - Lafferty, Eileen (Mrs. Russell C. Pickering), 1926-1927; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 59)
    - Cochran, Anne Jane [Class of 1929], 1926-1929; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 60)
    - Fitton, Martha (Mrs. Robert Kirby Whyte) [Class of 1928], 1926-1931; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 61)
    - Davison, Mary Thayer (Mrs. Charles Begole Cumings) - biographical information, 1926-1937; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 62)
    - Bohun, Irene Saunders - Class of 1929, 1927-1929; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - Bradley, Suzanne Thatcher (Mrs. Lawrence Nelson, Jr.) - Class of 1929, 1927-1929; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - Dwight, Eleanor [Class of 1929], 1927-1929; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 63)
    - Heuer, Louise, 1927-1929; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 64)
    - Lammers, Gertrude Risdon [Class of 1929], 1927-1929; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 65)
    - Three students posing on campus, 1927-1929; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 66)
    - Lauer, Jeanie Dean (Mrs. Paul F. Halpine), 1927-1930; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 67)
    - Chanute, Elaine (Mrs. David Case III) [Class of 1930], 1927-1931; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 68)
    - Broadwater, Antoinette Wilder (Mrs. Philip T. Clay, Jr.) - biographical information, 1927-1937; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 69)
    - Horst, Catherine L. (Mrs. Erik Holmberg) - wedding invitation, 1927-1937; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 70)
    - Junior class play - "The Merchant of Venice", 1928 March 17; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 28, Folder 31)
    - Howard, Elizabeth F. (Mrs. H. Robinson Safford, Jr.) - wedding invitation, 1928-1936; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 71)
    - Bovenizer, Eleanor (Mrs. George W. Armstrong) - biographical information, 1928-1937; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 28, Folder 32)
    - Lewthwaite, Cornelia Alexandra (Mrs. Julius L. Meier, Jr.) - marriage announcement, 1928-1938; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 72)
    - Class of 1929, Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 28, Folder 33)
    - Groups - Cupola Board, 1929; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 28, Folder 34)
    - Groups - French club, 1929; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 28, Folder 35)
    - Groups - Dramatic workshops, 1929; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 28, Folder 36)
    - Reunion - Class of 1928, 1929; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 28, Folder 37)
    - Simpson, Mary Reed, 1929; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Vereen, Mary [Class of 1929], Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 73)
    - Bovenizer, Dorothy Smith (Mrs. Gerald E. Donovan) - Class of 1929, 1929-1932; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 28, Folder 38)
    - Brinkman, Frances Marion - Class of 1931, 1929-1933; Series 2 Subsereis 6 (Box 28, Folder 39)
    - Howell, Katharine M. (Mrs. Joseph Walter Cooper) [Class of 1929], 1929-1934; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 74)
    - Alexander, Martha Barker (Mrs. Frank A. Garbode) - Class of 1929, 1929-1935; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 28, Folder 40)
    - Burke, Elizabeth "Betty" Ainsworth, 1929-1935; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 75)
    - Fickinger, Harriet Caroline (Mrs. H. R. Wells) - biographical information, 1929-1935; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 76)
    - Dunbar, Bertha (Mrs. John Robbins Speer), 1929-1936; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 77)
    - Foye, Alice (Mrs. Richard V. Scott) [Class of 1929], 1929-1936; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Haradan, Mary Elizabeth (Mrs. Howard Dale Kisner) [Class of 1929], 1929-1936; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Kochs, Elsa A. (Mrs. Frank B. Voris), 1929-1936; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Farnsley, Florence (Mrs. Willard Preston McNair) [Class of 1929], 1929-1937; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Kaiser, Marjorie [Class of 1929], 1929-1937; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Johnson, Margaret (Mrs. Barry Goldwater) [Class of 1929], 1929-1964; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Groups - Picnic Field House, 1930; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 28, Folder 41)
    - Groups - Tea House Activity, Circa 1930-1931; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 28, Folder 42)
    - School - Grand Daughters, Circa 1930-1931; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 28, Folder 43)
    - Student Organizations - Optima, Circa 1930-1931; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 28, Folder 44)
    - Bonthron, Mary Louise (Mrs. Neil Roderick McLeod) - marriage announcement, 1930-1932; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 28, Folder 45)
    - Chisholm, Virginia (Mrs. Andrew Ford), 1930-1935; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Duncan, Winifred Collier (Mrs. Charles Lewis Thompson) [Class of 1932], 1930-1935; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Armstrong, Katharine Julian - Class of 1934, 1930-1936; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 28, Folder 46)
    - Cannon, Mariam Winslow (Mrs. Robert Griffith Hayes) - biographical information, 1930-1936; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Koehn, Elizabeth (Mrs. Robert Maxwell Ingham, Jr.) - marriage announcement, 1930-1936; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Bayly, Nancy Belle (Mrs. Fritz H. Haradon, Jr.), 1930-1937; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 28, Folder 47)
    - Cable, Katherine Woodruff (Mrs. George Robert Lindfelt) [Class of 1932] - biographical information, 1930-1937; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Kuldell, Ethelyn (Mrs. George Frederick Hamman), 1930-1937; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Chisholm, Polly Levering (Mrs. John Cummings Wylly), 1930-1938; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Gilkeson, Susan (Mrs. Alan C. Caldwell, Jr.) - biographical information, 1930-1938; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Student on staircase (Nebraska Avenue campus), Circa 1930-1942; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Groups - 1905/1906 Alumni women at Gatesley, 1931; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 28, Folder 48)
    - Beattie, Mary Josephine - Class of 1935, 1931-1935; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 28, Folder 49)
    - Born, Patricia (Mrs. Lewis John Goodbody) - marriage announcement, 1931-1935; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 28, Folder 50)
    - Gordon, Isabel (Mrs. Edmond M. Sullivan) - newspaper clipping, 1931-1936; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Bonnell, Barbara Arms (Mrs. Thomas A. Musto), 1931-1937; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 28, Folder 51)
    - Cobb, Barbara Smith (Mrs. Clyde Henry Walsworth) [Class of 1933], 1931-1937; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Hoover, Marianne W. (Mrs. Carl Davis, Jr.) - wedding invitation, 1931-1937; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - Dexter, Dorothy Muriel (Mrs. George Thomson Aitken) [Class of 1934] - biographical information, 1931-1938; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Carter, Alice (Mrs. Ashford Todd, Jr.) [Class of 1932], Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - Burrow, Josephine Elizabeth (biographical information), 1932-1936; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - Butler, Laura Gilbert, 1932-1936; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - Benton, Anne (Mrs. William Belden Hagyard), 1932-1937; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 28, Folder 52)
    - Dallis, Epsie (Mrs. Harry William Buice), 1932-1937; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 37, Folder 23)
    - Davis, Mary Covode (Mrs. James Thomas Joyce, Jr.), 1932-1937; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 37, Folder 24)
    - Harris, Ruth (Mrs. Albert W. Adcock) - biographical information, 1932-1937; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 37, Folder 25)
    - Field, Elizabeth Ann (Mrs. Lester B. Knight, Jr.), 1933; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 37, Folder 26)
    - Groups - Dramatic Workshop with Miss Herriott, 1933-1934; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 37, Folder 27)
    - Andrews, Mary Isabelle and Fox, Dorothy Alice - Class of 1932 (biographical information), 1933-1937; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 28, Folder 53)
    - Atkins, Elizabeth Ann "Betty" - Class of 1935 (biographical information), 1933-1937; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 28, Folder 54)
    - Butler, Elizabeth "Betsy" Ann (Mrs. Hugo Wangelin) - biographical information, 1933-1937; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 37, Folder 28)
    - Group - Students crafting on campus, 1934 June 5; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 37, Folder 29)
    - Easley, Nancy Jane, 1934-1935; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 37, Folder 30)
    - Donaldson, Emily Craig [Class of 1936], 1934-1936; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 37, Folder 31)
    - Kimball, Doris L. (Mrs. Francis Reber Kenney), 1934-1936; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 37, Folder 32)
    - Cornell, Emily (Mrs. Henry Alpheus Drake) [Class of 1935] - biographical information, 1934-1937; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 37, Folder 33)
    - Kavanagh, Georgia Janet (Mrs. Robert L. Schmitz) - marriage announcement, 1934-1937; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 37, Folder 34)
    - Bowdry, Martha Murdock (Mrs. John Watts Maynor) - biographical information, 1934-1938; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 28, Folder 55)
    - Dawley, Gail, 1935-1936; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 37, Folder 35)
    - Foskett, Marianne Ferguson (Mrs. R. Wilson Voorhees) - biographical information, 1935-1937; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 37, Folder 36)
    - Arnold, Frances Hill, 1936-1937; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 28, Folder 56)
    - Fickinger, Mary (Mrs. Richard Elliott Templin) - biographical information, 1936-1937; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 37, Folder 37)
    - Lutz, Eleanor Burwell (Mrs. John P. Carter) [Class of 1936], 1936-1937; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 37, Folder 38)
    - Blankenhorn, Mary, 1937; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 28, Folder 57)
    - Bradford, Faith - Class of 1900 (Alumna Award information), 1937; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 28, Folder 58)
    - Groups - Drama Club dressed for Centenery Play, 1937; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 37, Folder 39)
    - Hutton, Nedenia, 1937; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 37, Folder 40)
    - Student Group, 1937; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 28, Folder 59)
    - Dean, Dorothy Dilworth (Mrs. William Minor Mason) - biographical information, 1937-1938; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 37, Folder 41)
    - Goshorn, Betty Jean, 1940; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 37, Folder 42)
    - Students gathered for the concert, Circa 1940s; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 37, Folder 43)
    - Students in art classroom, Circa 1940s; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 37, Folder 44)
    - Students in costumes for the Christmas performance, Circa 1940s; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 37, Folder 45)
    - Student Life 1940-1949, Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Athletic awards at Gatesley, Circa 1942-1946; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 37, Folder 46)
    - Chrysler Ladies (Auxiliary No. 5) supporting troops, Circa 1942-1946; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 37, Folder 47)
    - Domestic science laboratory, Circa 1942-1946; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 37, Folder 48)
    - Groups - Students on steps of MVS temporary location at Julius Garfinkel store on Massachusetts Avenue, Circa 1942-1946; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 37, Folder 49)
    - Students in the library at the 4340 Fordham dormitory, Circa 1942-1946; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 37, Folder 50)
    - Typewriting class, Circa 1942-1946; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 37, Folder 51)
    - Sewing lab (Spring Valley campus), Circa 1944; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 37, Folder 52)
    - Students in bedroom (Spring Valley campus), 1944; Sereis 2 Subseries 6 (Box 37, Folder 53)
    - Students in living room at Glenbrook Road (Spring Valley campus), Circa 1944; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 37, Folder 54)
    - Students preparing food in cooking lab, Circa late 1940s-1950s; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 37, Folder 55)
    - Student Life 1950-1959, Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Spring Valley Collection - Photos of Students & Mt. Vernon Seminary ca. 1950's to early 1970's, 1950-1970; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Ann Goldsmith's photographs of friends and "The Big Snow of 1958", 1958-1960; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 37, Folder 56)
    - Student Life 1960-1969, Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Student Life ca. 1960's - early 1970's (undated), ca. 1960-1970; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Student Life 1970-1979, Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Student Life ca. 1970's - early 1980's (Undated) [1/2], ca. 1970-1985; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Student Life ca. 1970's - early 1980's (Undated) [2/2], ca. 1970-1985; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Student Life Negatives ca. late 1970's - early 1980's, ca. 1970-1985; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Student Life Small Photo Sheets & Negatives ca. 1970's - early 1980's, ca. 1970-1985; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Students Studying and Working ca. 1970's - early 1980's (Undated), ca. 1970-1985; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Baker, Cissy, 1978-1998; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Baker, Cissy (Supporting Material - Stationery, Programs), 1978-1998; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Student Life 1980-1989, Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Student wedding photos, 1982-1995; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 37, Folder 57)
    - Student Portraits 1983, Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Student Life Negatives ca. late 1980's-early 1990's, ca. 1985-1995; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Student Life ca. late 1980's - early 1990's (Undated), ca. 1985-1995; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Randall, Laura, Circa 1988; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 28, Folder 60)
    - Allen, Mary Louise - Class of 1919 (70th reunion), 1989; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 28, Folder 61)
    - Student Protest - "No Affiliation", 1989; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Group of students, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 37, Folder 58)
    - Yearbook Photos 1990-1992 [1/2], Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Yearbook Photos 1990-1992 [2/2], Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Student Life 1990-1999, Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Storm Damage ca. 1991-1992, Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Holiday card featuring photographs of student groups from 1880s and 1994, Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 37, Folder 59)
    - Hwang, Unchu "Angie", 1994-1995; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 37, Folder 60)
    - Students and MVC Campus 1999, Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Women and Power, 1999 Fall; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 37, Folder 61)
    - Haines, Barbara and Porter, Sharon, undated; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 28, Folder 62)
    - Student Life, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Photo Albums, 1940-1990; 1955-1986; Series 2 Subseries 7
    - Class of 1940 Photo Album [1/9], Series 2 Subseries 7 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Class of 1940 Photo Album [2/9], Series 2 Subseries 7 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Class of 1940 Photo Album - "1955" [3/9], Series 2 Subseries 7 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Class of 1940 Photo Album - "1956 N.C." [4/9], Series 2 Subseries 7 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Class of 1940 Photo Album - "1965" [5/9], Series 2 Subseries 7 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Class of 1940 Photo Album - "1975" [6/9], Series 2 Subseries 7 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Class of 1940 Photo Album - "1980" [7/9], Series 2 Subseries 7 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Class of 1940 Photo Album - "1986 Shreveport" [8/9], Series 2 Subseries 7 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Class of 1940 Photo Album - "1990" [9/9], Series 2 Subseries 7 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Photo Album ca. 1980's, Series 2 Subseries 7 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Oversized Photos, 1900-1997; 1978-1997; Series 2 Subseries 8
    The materials in Box 29 were added to this collection later. These materials have been separately arranged in chronological order.
    - Unidentified Student ca. 1900, Series 2 Subseries 8 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Golden Jubilee Supper (Mayflower Hotel), 1925 May 23; Series 2 Subseries 8; Photograph is rolled and in a very fragile state. Conservation will be needed to fully view this photograph. (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Golden Jubilee Supper (Mayflower Hotel), 1925 May 23; Series 2 Subseries 8; Photograph is rolled and in a very fragile state. Conservation will be needed to fully view this photograph (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Golden Jubilee Supper (Mayflower Hotel), 1925 May 23; Series 2 Subseries 8; Photograph is rolled and in a very fragile state. Conservation will be needed to fully view this photograph (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Eleanor Roosevelt American School Association, 1933 April 30; Series 2 Subseries 8; Photograph is rolled and in a very fragile state. Conservation will be needed to fully view this photograph (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Centenery Dinner, 1937 November 5; Series 2 Subseries 8; Photograph is rolled and in a very fragile state. Conservation will be needed to fully view this photograph (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Class photo ca. 1950's, Series 2 Subseries 8 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Class of 1951, Series 2 Subseries 8 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Victoria Schuck Inauguration, 1978; Series 2 Subseries 8 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - "Mars 1980 - Elizabeth", Series 2 Subseries 8 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Student and Alumnus ca. 1980's (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Pages of Filmstrip Photos and Negatives ca. 1980-1989, Series 2 Subseries 8 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Bulletin Cover 1987, Series 2 Subseries 8 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Geiselman & 2 Unidentified Students at Commencement 1995, Series 2 Subseries 8 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - UN Association Certificate for MVC, 1995; Series 2 Subseries 8 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Linda Wilkins and Heather Ellsworth in Celebration of Prestigious African American Women, 1996; Series 2 Subseries 8 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Class of 1997 Photo Books, Series 2 Subseries 8 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Bzeshkovally, Catherine, undated; Series 2 Subseries 8 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Campus building (Foxhall Road campus), undated; Series 2 Subseries 8 (Box 39, Folder 8)